What is that thing?!
Let's get out of here!
Wait! You might get killed, too!
Then what are we supposed to do?!
Is there no other way out?!
How the hell am I supposed to know?!
Two of us are already dead!
Nobody move! If you do, it'll attack again!
Joohee! Joohee!
That was a close one.
If you hadn't noticed what was happening,
we'd all be dead.
Didn't you yell because you'd figured it out?
No... It just seemed dangerous...
Mr. Song, your arm!
If I grit my teeth, it's not too bad.
Can you stop the bleeding, though?
I was hoping to ask Joohee, but...
she doesn't handle pressure well.
That's why she only takes part in easy raids,
despite being a B-Rank healer.
I've been through two or three
B-Rank dungeons myself...
And that might be an A-Rank foe... or even S.
The commandments of the Cartenon Temple
written on that tablet...
"First, revere God. Second, praise God."
"Third, prove your faith to God."
"Those who do not follow these
laws will not leave alive."
Mr. Song... The god it's talking about...
It's probably that thing, isn't it?
Over ten years ago, tunnels known as gates
that connected our world to
an alternate dimension appeared,
giving rise to a number of supernatural
phenomena throughout the world.
Those who awaken to special powers,
known as hunters, are a prime example.
They are tasked with defeating the beasts
that lie within the dungeons through gates,
and a hunter's power,
once active, never changes.
But at times, on the other side of a gate,
one finds monsters who inspire
something beyond mere terror—
something akin to absolute despair.
Did you watch it?
Oh, the video?
What were you doing?
You almost got marked as late.
Nothing special.
Jinah, your brother's a hunter, right?
Sure is.
Well, that said, he's an E-Rank hunter...
So he's always getting hurt real bad.
It seems like a lot of trouble.
He came home covered
in bandages the other day!
Why are you asking, anyway?
No real reason.
I bet I could do a better job...
That thing is too strong to fight.
Let's collect ourselves and
search for a way out of here.
It won't be—
I'm not just gonna die in here!
I finally managed to land a contract
with a major guild!
I can't afford to bite it like this!
What are you doing?! You mustn't move!
I can pull this off!
I'm pretty confident in my speed.
I'll get it before it gets me!
Damn it!
I think this means it could
wipe us all out if it felt like it.
Easily, too. Like stepping on a bug.
Then why doesn't it kill us right now?
It has the strength to kill us, but it hasn't.
There's something different about it compared
to most beasts, which attack on sight.
Mr. Song, what was the first
commandment again?
The commandments?
I think the first one was to revere God.
God...
This dungeon has its own rules.
What are you doing?!
If I'm right about this...
You need to stop—
From how you look, you haven't
given up on surviving this.
Everyone! Bow your heads
toward the statue, please!
Bow our heads?
What the hell are you talking about?
Did you figure out something?
I think so. As long as you keep
your head low, it won't attack.
"Revere God." Just like the commandment says.
You're sure about this?
Yes... For now.
In that case...
This is gonna save us? This is all it takes?
Damn, that's freaky!
Its expression changed?
It's not doing anything.
Hey! Don't just get up!
Look! It's not attacking anymore!
Is it really over?
Are we safe now?
All right!
We're saved!
We can go home!
No... There's still...
I thought it was over!
Sung, what now?! You have
some kind of plan, right?
N-Not at all!
But it's probably a bad idea to break
the commandments they set!
The second was to praise God!
That's what we need to figure out!
Praise him?!
How, exactly?
Let me give this a try.
I've been studying ethnology.
There are a few extolments
for gods that come to mind.
O God, our great ruler
who brings order to the world...
Is it working?
I think it might be slowing down?
Show us the path of truth.
Wait. That's...
Thy will be done...
Those words don't apply to this god!
We revere and honor thee!
O God, our great ruler
who brings order to the world!
Shit!
Run for it!
It's too dangerous to bunch up!
Spread out!
Right!
Let's run, Joohee!
I can't die like this!
I've got family waiting for me!
I should be safe over here, right?
Hey, Park! Behind you!
Park!
Praise God... Praise God...
What is there to praise about that thing?!
It's basically a devil!
But I can't leave Joohee alone.
I need some kind of clue.
Spears... Axes...
Hammers... Swords... Instruments...
Instruments?
Everyone! Run to the statues
with instruments!
The instruments?
Is it... playing?
Hey! The statues with
instruments won't attack!
Damn it all...
Please, play your music! Hurry!
Does it not work if there's two people?
You stay here, Joohee!
Jinwoo!
Over there!
Not there!
No!
Jinwoo!
Not... yet...
Not yet!
I guess this is what was meant by praise?
Jinwoo! Are you okay?!
Yeah... Barely.
Jinwoo...
Yeah?
Your leg...
That's enough, Joohee. I'll be fine.
What are you saying?! I'm going to heal you!
Joohee...
What a nightmare.
It really is.
It's a shame about your arm.
But you made a careless call as our leader.
I guess it's just karma.
That's awful!
Kim, you were the one who—
Hey, we all decided together!
And I remember how you voted.
I was the one who made the final call.
I'm responsible for everything
that's happened here.
This is no time to be arguing.
There's still one more commandment.
What's going on now?!
An earthquake?!
What the hell is that?!
An altar.
They come up all the time in legends...
for offering treasure
and sacrifices to the gods.
The third commandment.
"Prove your faith to God."
Even an idiot like me knows
what the move is here.
We've gotta offer up a sacrifice,
ain't that right, Sung?
I saw a man who was bragging about his wife
before we came in here split down the middle.
And he wasn't the only one!
You said it yourself, didn't you?
Well, time to take responsibility, Leader.
Kim, that's—
Enough out of you, buddy!
Fine. Let me go myself.
This isn't Mr. Song's fault alone.
We took a vote to decide to come here!
What's happening now?
Sung! Is there anything else I need to do?
What is this? Didn't we need a sacrifice?
Sorry. I'd like to examine the altar,
so could you help me over to it?
Get me right next to it, please.
B-But then, won't we...
I don't think anything will happen.
Did you figure something out?
Not yet, no...
If we wait here, is anyone
likely to come rescue us?
The gate will have been open
for a week as of today.
They'll probably start moving again
before anyone comes for us.
It takes seven days for a gate
to open up all the way.
That's what's called a dungeon break.
When that happens, the beasts are
able to cross over to the other side.
The other objective of raids
is to defeat the dungeon boss
and shut the gate down
before that time is up.
Which means if we fail here...
That thing will be able to enter our world.
Hello!
Oh, Miss Sung! It's wonderful
how you visit every day.
Mom! I'm here again.
Song-yi was late to class today.
She said she'd had stuff to do,
but I'm sure she just overslept!
Oh, and in the national test...
Could you two come over here, please?
We probably need a flame
to light up for each one of us.
If anything's going to happen,
it'll be after that.
The door's open.
Can we leave?
Unless this is a trap, too...
What was that sound?!
Th-The statues are coming this way!
What do we do?!
Why are they coming after us?!
No!
Joohee, don't close your eyes!
They won't move if you're watching them!
It works like that old children's game.
Everyone, keep your eyes on the statues!
Nooo!
Hey!
Wait!
What's going on here, Sung?!
The door closed a bit,
but I think she made it out!
Why?
The blue flames have been
dying out over time.
One of the orange ones went out
when someone escaped.
The first order was to revere.
The second was to praise.
The third is to prove our faith...
It must be a trap.
Causing danger and fear,
and then offering a false sense of hope...
Maybe it's testing our faith in this god.
I can't... I can't do this!
Jeongho!
Hey!
Don't!
You can't move!
If anyone else leaves,
we'll have blind spots!
What is happening here, Sung?!
We need an explanation!
As long as we keep our eyes on the statues
and don't move, we'll be safe!
The blue flames are a timer.
When they're all gone, we'll all make it out!
Isn't there a chance we'll be
trapped in here once they go out, too?
I'll be honest, I didn't expect you,
our weakest member,
to pull off as much as you've managed.
The only reason we're alive
at all is thanks to you.
Kim...
But I've got a family waiting for me!
I can't die just yet!
I wanna make it home alive!
I can't take any more of this!
I'm sorry!
Why?
Not yet!
We have to survive this!
I've managed to make it before, somehow!
The two of you should go.
Mr. Song?
I think the doors will stay open
as long as one of us remains here.
You two still have long lives
ahead of you. You should go.
Joohee, look after Sung for me.
R-Right!
No... Oh, no... No...
My legs... gave out on me...
You must've over-exerted
yourself healing Sung.
Mr. Song. Take Joohee and go.
I just said I'm going to stay—
Then who's going to carry Joohee out?!
There's no time. Hurry!
You can't, Jinwoo!
In that case, it should be me—
I promised to take you out to eat, didn't I?
Use this to buy yourself dinner.
And when I get out of here,
I'll be along to collect the change.
How can you even say—
I'm sorry. But it looks like
we really are out of time.
Please.
Good. I'm the only one who has to die.
If I'd known this was gonna happen,
I would've enrolled in a juicier
life insurance package.
I'll take at least one of you down with me...
So bring it on!
I've always been the weakest.
And I've been mocked for it,
time and time again.
But I've always tried as hard as I could.
And now...
This is bullshit.
It's bullshit! This is such bullshit!
I tried to be stronger...
but I couldn't.
And even then,
I gave it my all to get this far!
You couldn't take any more?
We all felt the same way!
All you were doing was
justifying your own selfishness!
That gratitude was purely superficial.
It's always the most selfish
people who benefit the most!
I have a family, too!
I wanted to make it home alive, too!
It's good that I'm the only one
who has to die?
How could you think that,
you stupid hypocrite?!
No. I don't wanna die.
If... If I had one more chance...